[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A teaser commercial was released as a trailer for Resident Evil: Apocalypse. It was marketed as a skin care product to make you look younger. What was the name of the product?", "correct_answer": "Regenerate", "incorrect_answers": ["Regenerist", "Fountain of Youth", "Rejuvinate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Alexs parents recognize their son after so many years in the 2008 animated comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "By his beauty mark", "incorrect_answers": ["By his eyes", "By his voice", "By his teeth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the most diverse and abundant group of organisms on Earth. Its members reproduce so fast that they can double their number as quickly as every 10 minutes.", "correct_answer": "Bacteria", "incorrect_answers": ["Viruses", "Algae", "Fungi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the popular ship from the ultraexpensive 2006 movie Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Mans Chest?", "correct_answer": "Black Pearl", "incorrect_answers": ["Old Ramshackle", "Dead Mans Chest", "Sparrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although Hillary Clinton implied in CBS 60 minutes that she did not like this song, it was on the soundtrack to Sleepless in Seattle.", "correct_answer": "Stand By Your Man", "incorrect_answers": ["I Go to Pieces", "Crazy", "The Missouri Waltz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Chinese actor starred in the 2006 Chinese movie Curse of the Golden Flower, a.k.a. When Golden Armour Covers the Entire City?", "correct_answer": "Chow Yun-Fat", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackie Chan", "Jet Li", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which President of the United States does Anthony Hopkins portray in Steven Spielbergs historical drama Amistad?", "correct_answer": "John Quincy Adams", "incorrect_answers": ["John Adams", "Abraham Lincoln", "Martin Van Buren"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which Lord of the Rings movie does Boromir die?", "correct_answer": "The Fellowship of the Ring", "incorrect_answers": ["Return of the King", "The Two Towers", "He doesnt die."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which capital city also refers to an open source project for the Java platform?", "correct_answer": "Jakarta", "incorrect_answers": ["Rome", "Mexico", "Cairo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the difference between the digestion of kangaroos and the digestion of ruminants?", "correct_answer": "Kangaroos do not release methane.", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing", "Kangaroos need to consume some animal matter to provide essential digestive bacteria.", "Kangaroos digest plant matter five times faster than ruminants do."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Guinness Book of World Records, the heaviest wild bear was caught in 1960 and weighed 1,960 lbs (890 kg). What was its length?", "correct_answer": "Over 11 feet (3,40 m) tall", "incorrect_answers": ["Over 12 feet (3,70 m) tall", "Over 9 feet (2,70 m) tall", "Over 10 feet (3 m) tall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Siddhartha in Bernardo Bertoluccis movie Little Buddha?", "correct_answer": "Keanu Reeves", "incorrect_answers": ["Olivier Martinez", "Joseph Fiennes", "Ralph Fiennes"]}]